ISABELLA Webdeweloper.

CONTACT

Isabella Molterer Salzburg - Austria +43660 3569577 isabella.molterer@gmail.com

- () /isabella-molterer
- in /isabella-molterer
- (c) /re_bella



Hello! I am Isabella, a web developer based in Salzburg, Austria. With a master's degree in Web Engineering, I specialize in full-stack web development, with a keen focus on frontend development.

Passionate about web development and design, I am driven to learn new technologies and tackle challenging projects.



EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Web Developer

Nolimits Digital Business GmbH

2021 - NOW

Designing and developing websites using Wordpress and Shopware

Web Developer Internship

Atikon EDV & Marketing GmbH

11.02.2019-28.06.2019

Designing and developing websites using a custom CMS framework

Web Developer Internship

Atikon EDV & Marketing GmbH

30.06.2018-30.09.2018

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Engineering

University of Applied Sciences Salzburg 2019-2022

Bachelor of Science in Engineering

University of Applied Sciences Hagenberg 2016-2019

SKILLS

Web Technologies

HTML5

CSS, SCSS, SASS, Bootstrap ECMAScript, TypeScript

GG

Python

Ruby On Rails

MySQL

Webpack

Node

Nest.js, Express.js, Vue.js

Symfony

Wordpress

Shopware

Other Tools

Docker

Git

Figma, Invision, AdobeXD